True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (9, 11, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 0, Sentence Total: 1
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 1, Entity FN: 2
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 1, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (6, 7, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'GPE'), (10, 20, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 0, Sentence Total: 2
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 3, Entity FN: 4
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 3, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 1, Sentence Total: 3
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 3, Entity FN: 4
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 3, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (15, 16, 'LOC'), (21, 22, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 1, Sentence Total: 4
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 4, Entity FN: 7
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 4, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(7, 8, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 1, Sentence Total: 5
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 4, Entity FN: 8
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 4, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG'), (3, 5, 'PERSON'), (6, 7, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG'), (4, 11, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 1, Sentence Total: 6
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 6, Entity FN: 11
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 6, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 4, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 1, Sentence Total: 7
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 7, Entity FN: 12
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 7, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (3, 4, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 1, Sentence Total: 8
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 8, Entity FN: 14
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 8, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 2, Sentence Total: 9
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 8, Entity FN: 14
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 8, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(5, 6, 'GPE'), (6, 9, 'PERSON'), (11, 12, 'LOC'), (17, 18, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(3, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 2, Sentence Total: 10
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 9, Entity FN: 18
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 9, Token True Total: 0

Processing Sentence: Tehran denies the allegation .
True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 2, Sentence Total: 11
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 10, Entity FN: 19
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 10, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(6, 7, 'LOC'), (25, 26, 'PERSON'), (34, 35, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 2, Sentence Total: 12
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 10, Entity FN: 22
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 10, Token True Total: 0

Processing Sentence: Earthquakes are common in Turkey .
True Entities: [(4, 5, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 11, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 2, Sentence Total: 13
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 11, Entity FN: 23
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 11, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 14
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 11, Entity FN: 23
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 11, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 4, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 15
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 12, Entity FN: 24
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 12, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 16
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 13, Entity FN: 25
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 13, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG'), (7, 8, 'LOC'), (13, 15, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 2, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 17
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 14, Entity FN: 28
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 14, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (2, 7, 'PERSON'), (8, 10, 'PERSON'), (11, 12, 'LOC'), (13, 14, 'DATE'), (15, 16, 'LOC'), (21, 24, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 18
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 15, Entity FN: 35
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 15, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (21, 22, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 19
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 16, Entity FN: 37
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 16, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'PERSON'), (1, 2, 'LOC'), (8, 9, 'DATE'), (12, 14, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 20
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 17, Entity FN: 41
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 17, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'DATE'), (12, 13, 'LOC'), (25, 26, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 21
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 18, Entity FN: 44
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 18, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'LOC'), (4, 5, 'GPE'), (6, 7, 'ORG'), (11, 12, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 22
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 19, Entity FN: 48
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 19, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'LOC'), (7, 8, 'LOC'), (31, 32, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 3, Sentence Total: 23
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 20, Entity FN: 51
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 20, Token True Total: 0

Processing Sentence: They were set to expire next week .
True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 4, Sentence Total: 24
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 20, Entity FN: 51
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 20, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(2, 6, 'ORG'), (15, 16, 'GPE'), (16, 17, 'PERSON'), (18, 20, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 4, Sentence Total: 25
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 21, Entity FN: 55
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 21, Token True Total: 0

Processing Sentence: Iran is the world 's fourth-largest oil exporter .
True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 4, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 4, Sentence Total: 26
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 22, Entity FN: 56
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 22, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(4, 6, 'ORG'), (8, 10, 'PERSON'), (17, 19, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 14, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 4, Sentence Total: 27
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 23, Entity FN: 59
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 23, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'LOC'), (7, 8, 'DATE'), (15, 17, 'LOC'), (27, 28, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 4, Sentence Total: 28
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 24, Entity FN: 63
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 24, Token True Total: 0

True Entities: [(2, 4, 'ORG'), (7, 9, 'PERSON'), (10, 11, 'DATE'), (16, 17, 'LOC'), (24, 25, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 4, Sentence Total: 29
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 25, Entity FN: 68
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 25, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 5, Sentence Total: 30
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 25, Entity FN: 68
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 25, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 6, Sentence Total: 31
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 25, Entity FN: 68
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 25, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(6, 7, 'ORG'), (11, 12, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(6, 9, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 6, Sentence Total: 32
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 26, Entity FN: 70
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 26, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (3, 4, 'LOC'), (10, 12, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 6, Sentence Total: 33
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 27, Entity FN: 73
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 27, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 7, Sentence Total: 34
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 27, Entity FN: 73
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 27, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'LOC'), (9, 10, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 7, Sentence Total: 35
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 28, Entity FN: 75
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 28, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'ORG'), (4, 6, 'PERSON'), (28, 29, 'LOC'), (31, 33, 'ORG'), (35, 36, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG'), (4, 9, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 7, Sentence Total: 36
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 30, Entity FN: 80
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 30, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(23, 24, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 7, Sentence Total: 37
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 30, Entity FN: 81
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 30, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 38
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 30, Entity FN: 81
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 30, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(9, 10, 'DATE'), (16, 17, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 39
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 30, Entity FN: 83
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 30, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'ORG'), (6, 7, 'LOC'), (17, 18, 'ORG'), (24, 25, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 13, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 40
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 31, Entity FN: 87
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 31, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(5, 6, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(2, 9, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 41
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 32, Entity FN: 88
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 32, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (10, 11, 'ORG'), (17, 18, 'GPE'), (18, 19, 'PERSON'), (20, 22, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 42
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 33, Entity FN: 93
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 33, Token True Total: 1

Processing Sentence: The building was constructed in 1890 as a synagogue .
True Entities: [(5, 6, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 12, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 43
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 34, Entity FN: 94
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 34, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: [(4, 7, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 44
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 35, Entity FN: 94
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 35, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (3, 4, 'DATE'), (18, 19, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 8, Sentence Total: 45
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 36, Entity FN: 97
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 36, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 46
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 36, Entity FN: 97
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 36, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(20, 21, 'LOC'), (22, 23, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 47
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 36, Entity FN: 99
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 36, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (2, 4, 'ORG'), (5, 7, 'PERSON'), (31, 32, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 48
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 37, Entity FN: 103
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 37, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(4, 6, 'PERSON'), (9, 10, 'DATE'), (33, 34, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 7, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 49
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 38, Entity FN: 106
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 38, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(13, 16, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 50
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 38, Entity FN: 107
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 38, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(5, 7, 'LOC'), (12, 13, 'LOC'), (14, 16, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 9, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 51
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 39, Entity FN: 110
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 39, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG'), (8, 9, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 52
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 40, Entity FN: 112
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 40, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'ORG'), (7, 8, 'ORG'), (12, 14, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 14, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 53
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 41, Entity FN: 115
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 41, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'GPE'), (3, 4, 'PERSON'), (5, 7, 'PERSON'), (8, 9, 'DATE'), (18, 19, 'GPE'), (22, 24, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 54
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 42, Entity FN: 121
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 42, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(7, 8, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 55
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 42, Entity FN: 122
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 42, Token True Total: 1

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'PERSON'), (3, 4, 'DATE'), (10, 12, 'EVENT'), (13, 15, 'PERSON'), (16, 17, 'LOC'), (21, 22, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 56
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 43, Entity FN: 128
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 43, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(2, 5, 'PERSON'), (19, 20, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 57
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 44, Entity FN: 130
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 44, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (15, 16, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 58
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 45, Entity FN: 132
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 45, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (1, 4, 'PERSON'), (15, 16, 'GPE'), (22, 23, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 59
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 46, Entity FN: 136
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 46, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG'), (4, 6, 'PERSON'), (8, 9, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(2, 9, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 60
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 47, Entity FN: 139
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 47, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (4, 5, 'LOC'), (7, 8, 'GPE'), (10, 12, 'PERSON'), (19, 20, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'GPE'), (4, 10, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 61
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 49, Entity FN: 144
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 49, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'GPE'), (3, 4, 'PERSON'), (5, 7, 'PERSON'), (8, 9, 'DATE'), (18, 19, 'GPE'), (22, 24, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 9, Sentence Total: 62
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 50, Entity FN: 150
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 50, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 63
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 50, Entity FN: 150
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 50, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'PERSON'), (2, 3, 'DATE'), (10, 11, 'GPE'), (22, 23, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 64
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 51, Entity FN: 154
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 51, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (3, 5, 'PERSON'), (12, 13, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 65
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 52, Entity FN: 157
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 52, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(4, 6, 'PERSON'), (8, 9, 'GPE'), (9, 10, 'DATE'), (13, 15, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 11, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 66
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 53, Entity FN: 161
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 53, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(5, 6, 'LOC'), (7, 8, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 67
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 53, Entity FN: 163
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 53, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(8, 9, 'LOC'), (13, 14, 'DATE'), (15, 17, 'LOC'), (18, 21, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 68
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 54, Entity FN: 167
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 54, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'LOC'), (3, 4, 'GPE'), (4, 5, 'PERSON'), (6, 8, 'PERSON'), (13, 14, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 2, 'LOC'), (3, 8, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 69
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 56, Entity FN: 172
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 56, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(5, 6, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 10, Sentence Total: 70
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 56, Entity FN: 173
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 56, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 11, Sentence Total: 71
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 56, Entity FN: 173
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 56, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (2, 3, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 11, Sentence Total: 72
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 57, Entity FN: 175
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 57, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 73
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 57, Entity FN: 175
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 57, Token True Total: 2

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (5, 9, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 74
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 58, Entity FN: 177
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 58, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(4, 5, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(2, 12, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 75
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 59, Entity FN: 178
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 59, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG'), (7, 8, 'GPE'), (10, 11, 'GPE'), (13, 14, 'GPE'), (17, 18, 'DATE'), (19, 20, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 4, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 76
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 60, Entity FN: 184
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 60, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'DATE'), (28, 29, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 77
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 60, Entity FN: 186
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 60, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (2, 6, 'PERSON'), (11, 14, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 78
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 61, Entity FN: 189
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 61, Token True Total: 3

Processing Sentence: The girl was first stricken in January .
True Entities: [(6, 7, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 79
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 61, Entity FN: 190
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 61, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(5, 7, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(2, 8, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 80
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 62, Entity FN: 191
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 62, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'PERSON'), (4, 5, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(3, 12, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 81
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 63, Entity FN: 193
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 63, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(7, 8, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 82
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 63, Entity FN: 194
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 63, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (15, 16, 'LOC'), (17, 18, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 4, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 83
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 64, Entity FN: 197
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 64, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(4, 5, 'LOC'), (6, 8, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(3, 6, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 84
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 65, Entity FN: 199
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 65, Token True Total: 3

True Entities: [(2, 4, 'PERSON'), (7, 9, 'DATE'), (23, 27, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 85
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 65, Entity FN: 202
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 65, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 86
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 66, Entity FN: 203
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 66, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'DATE'), (7, 8, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 12, Sentence Total: 87
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 66, Entity FN: 205
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 66, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 88
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 66, Entity FN: 205
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 66, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'GPE'), (3, 6, 'ORG'), (6, 7, 'DATE'), (11, 12, 'GPE'), (12, 14, 'ORG'), (18, 20, 'LOC'), (24, 26, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 9, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 89
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 67, Entity FN: 212
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 67, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'LOC'), (6, 7, 'ORG'), (9, 10, 'LOC'), (21, 23, 'PERSON'), (30, 31, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 90
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 68, Entity FN: 217
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 68, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(6, 7, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 91
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 68, Entity FN: 218
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 68, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(8, 10, 'ORG'), (13, 15, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 92
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 68, Entity FN: 220
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 68, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'PERSON'), (11, 12, 'DATE'), (23, 24, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 93
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 69, Entity FN: 223
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 69, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (31, 33, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 94
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 70, Entity FN: 225
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 70, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(5, 7, 'PERSON'), (18, 20, 'PERSON'), (24, 25, 'LOC'), (26, 27, 'DATE'), (34, 35, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(2, 8, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 95
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 71, Entity FN: 230
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 71, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (15, 16, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 13, Sentence Total: 96
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 72, Entity FN: 232
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 72, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 97
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 72, Entity FN: 232
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 72, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG'), (7, 9, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 98
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 73, Entity FN: 234
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 73, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'LOC'), (5, 7, 'DATE'), (17, 18, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(4, 11, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 99
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 74, Entity FN: 237
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 74, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(7, 9, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 100
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 74, Entity FN: 238
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 74, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (10, 11, 'ORG'), (12, 14, 'LOC'), (16, 18, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 101
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 75, Entity FN: 242
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 75, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'DATE'), (10, 12, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 102
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 76, Entity FN: 244
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 76, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(19, 21, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 103
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 76, Entity FN: 245
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 76, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 104
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 77, Entity FN: 246
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 77, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (7, 8, 'DATE'), (17, 18, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 105
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 78, Entity FN: 249
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 78, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(11, 12, 'LOC'), (14, 16, 'ORG'), (19, 20, 'GPE'), (23, 24, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 106
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 78, Entity FN: 253
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 78, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(18, 20, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 107
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 78, Entity FN: 254
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 78, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (2, 4, 'ORG'), (6, 7, 'DATE'), (10, 12, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 2, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 108
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 79, Entity FN: 258
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 79, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'DATE'), (8, 9, 'LOC'), (13, 14, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 10, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 109
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 80, Entity FN: 261
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 80, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(3, 5, 'PERSON'), (6, 8, 'PERSON'), (10, 12, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 110
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 81, Entity FN: 264
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 81, Token True Total: 4

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (12, 14, 'PERSON'), (18, 20, 'ORG'), (27, 29, 'LOC'), (30, 31, 'LOC'), (33, 34, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 9, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 111
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 82, Entity FN: 270
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 82, Token True Total: 5

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (1, 4, 'PERSON'), (6, 7, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 112
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 83, Entity FN: 273
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 83, Token True Total: 5

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'PERSON'), (5, 8, 'PERSON'), (9, 12, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 113
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 84, Entity FN: 276
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 84, Token True Total: 5

True Entities: [(2, 3, 'LOC'), (6, 7, 'GPE'), (12, 13, 'LOC'), (14, 15, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 114
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 85, Entity FN: 280
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 85, Token True Total: 5

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'DATE'), (14, 15, 'LOC'), (21, 22, 'LOC'), (24, 25, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 115
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 86, Entity FN: 284
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 86, Token True Total: 5

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (9, 10, 'ORG'), (15, 16, 'LOC'), (24, 25, 'GPE'), (32, 33, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 116
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 86, Entity FN: 289
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 86, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (6, 8, 'PERSON'), (13, 14, 'DATE'), (41, 42, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 2, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 14, Sentence Total: 117
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 87, Entity FN: 293
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 87, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 118
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 87, Entity FN: 293
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 87, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 119
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 88, Entity FN: 293
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 88, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(8, 9, 'ORG'), (17, 18, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 120
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 88, Entity FN: 295
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 88, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (3, 5, 'PERSON'), (8, 9, 'GPE'), (9, 12, 'PERSON'), (14, 15, 'GPE'), (24, 25, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 121
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 89, Entity FN: 301
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 89, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 122
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 90, Entity FN: 302
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 90, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(11, 12, 'DATE'), (14, 15, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 123
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 90, Entity FN: 304
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 90, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG'), (10, 11, 'GPE'), (14, 15, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 124
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 91, Entity FN: 307
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 91, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG'), (4, 5, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG'), (4, 7, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 125
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 93, Entity FN: 309
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 93, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (1, 3, 'ORG'), (4, 7, 'PERSON'), (10, 11, 'DATE'), (17, 18, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 126
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 94, Entity FN: 314
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 94, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'DATE'), (2, 3, 'LOC'), (15, 16, 'PERSON'), (16, 17, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 127
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 95, Entity FN: 318
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 95, Token True Total: 6

Processing Sentence: The bombing was the second in recent days .
True Entities: [(6, 7, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 128
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 95, Entity FN: 319
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 95, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 2, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 129
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 96, Entity FN: 320
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 96, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: [(4, 14, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 130
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 97, Entity FN: 320
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 97, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (17, 18, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 131
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 98, Entity FN: 322
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 98, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(26, 27, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 132
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 98, Entity FN: 323
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 98, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'LOC'), (3, 4, 'LOC'), (14, 15, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 133
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 99, Entity FN: 326
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 99, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 134
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 100, Entity FN: 327
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 100, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(12, 13, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 135
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 100, Entity FN: 328
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 100, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (11, 13, 'PERSON'), (17, 18, 'LOC'), (20, 22, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 136
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 101, Entity FN: 332
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 101, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(14, 16, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 137
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 101, Entity FN: 333
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 101, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (3, 6, 'PERSON'), (7, 9, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 138
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 102, Entity FN: 336
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 102, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(5, 7, 'PERSON'), (11, 12, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 139
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 102, Entity FN: 338
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 102, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'PERSON'), (5, 6, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(2, 7, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 140
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 103, Entity FN: 340
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 103, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(6, 7, 'LOC'), (13, 15, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 141
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 103, Entity FN: 342
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 103, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 4, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 142
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 104, Entity FN: 343
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 104, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(14, 15, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 143
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 104, Entity FN: 344
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 104, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 2, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 15, Sentence Total: 144
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 105, Entity FN: 345
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 105, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 16, Sentence Total: 145
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 105, Entity FN: 345
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 105, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 2, 'PERSON'), (10, 11, 'LOC'), (11, 12, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 8, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 16, Sentence Total: 146
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 106, Entity FN: 348
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 106, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 147
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 106, Entity FN: 348
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 106, Token True Total: 6

True Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG'), (3, 5, 'PERSON'), (18, 19, 'GPE'), (23, 24, 'PERSON'), (24, 27, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 148
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 107, Entity FN: 353
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 107, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(5, 6, 'LOC'), (14, 15, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 149
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 107, Entity FN: 355
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 107, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 150
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 108, Entity FN: 356
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 108, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(0, 4, 'ORG'), (22, 23, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 151
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 109, Entity FN: 358
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 109, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(6, 7, 'DATE'), (18, 19, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 152
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 109, Entity FN: 360
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 109, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (24, 25, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 5, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 153
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 110, Entity FN: 362
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 110, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'LOC'), (5, 7, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 6, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 154
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 111, Entity FN: 364
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 111, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 155
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 112, Entity FN: 365
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 112, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(11, 15, 'ORG'), (19, 21, 'PERSON'), (27, 28, 'DATE'), (31, 32, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 156
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 112, Entity FN: 369
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 112, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(3, 4, 'LOC'), (6, 7, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 157
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 112, Entity FN: 371
Token Correct: 0, Token Pred Total: 112, Token True Total: 7

True Entities: [(0, 4, 'ORG'), (9, 10, 'DATE'), (17, 18, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'ORG')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 158
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 113, Entity FN: 374
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 113, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: [(10, 11, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 159
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 113, Entity FN: 375
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 113, Token True Total: 8

Processing Sentence: Shi'ite leaders have not responded to the demands .
True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 160
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 113, Entity FN: 376
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 113, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: [(1, 2, 'GPE'), (4, 6, 'ORG'), (11, 13, 'PERSON')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'ORG'), (8, 17, 'PERSON')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 161
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 115, Entity FN: 379
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 115, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'ORG'), (2, 3, 'EVENT'), (8, 9, 'GPE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'LOC')]
Sentence Correct: 17, Sentence Total: 162
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 116, Entity FN: 382
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 116, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: []
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 18, Sentence Total: 163
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 116, Entity FN: 382
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 116, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: [(0, 1, 'GPE'), (1, 2, 'PERSON'), (3, 5, 'PERSON'), (11, 12, 'ORG')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 7, 'GPE')]
Sentence Correct: 18, Sentence Total: 164
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 117, Enti
ty FN: 386
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 117, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: [(1, 3, 'ORG'), (4, 5, 'DATE')]
Predicted Entities: [(0, 3, 'PERSON'), (4, 11, 'DATE')]
Sentence Correct: 18, Sentence Total: 165
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 119, Entity FN: 388
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 119, Token True Total: 8

True Entities: [(6, 8, 'DATE'), (22, 23, 'LOC')]
Predicted Entities: []
Sentence Correct: 18, Sentence Total: 166
Entity TP: 0, Entity FP: 119, Entity FN: 390
Token Correct: 1, Token Pred Total: 119, Token True Total: 8